[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 36]
As
Ze Shui from ten thousand years ago
and Luo Ning ten thousand years later,
I
am here
to pardon
all Aquatic Demons
and
pardon
Fu
ten thousand years later.
Luo Ning!
I really want you to pay with your life for Luo Ning.
Even if you die a thousand or ten thousand times,
you can't atone for your sin.
The only reason I won't kill you
is that Luo Ning forgave you.
But I
will never forgive you.
Luo Ning.
Tell me.
Did I escort the bride for nothing?
It would've been fine if somebody stole her away.
We can steal her back.
Why
did she lose her life?
I thought it was not safe
when she said she wanted to marry the Demon King.
But I never thought
that Luo Ning would be with
Fu.
It's strange.
Fu is not the Demon King.
How can his spell be lifted
after being with Luo Ning?
Fu has the power of the Demon King,
the one
who had a grudge with Ze Shui.
But what's strange now is that
after Luo Ning died,
there is no immortal energy left.
Could it have fallen somewhere?
It took her last wish before she died
and went there.
Impossible.
With Luo Ge's cultivation,
how could he not find the immortal energy?
Luo Ge has only one sister.
Who wouldn't be sad?
I heard that
Immortal Master was so sad that he didn't come out for days.
Take a look.
This is the Lily Magnolia Perfume I specially made.
It can dispel cold and clear your nose.
Are you
suffering from fever, lung problem,
and a stuffy nose
because you're worried about my brother?
I made this specially for you.
Am I filial?
I said no to your marriage,
but you insisted.
In that case,
let the man you love
pay with his life.
It's something for me, too.
OK?
For the sake of the clan,
for you,
Luo Ning was willing to sacrifice herself.
But now, your obsession
attracted the evil spirit.
It also caused Luo Ning's death.
Although Luo Ge spared you,
I can't let it go.
When you get better,
I'll go with you to get punished at the Immortal Palace.
No punishment
is too much.
Fu,
I've removed the evil spirit for you.
But let me remind you.
Never
make contact with the evil creature under the Four Seasons Monument.
The curse has been lifted.
I owe my whole life
to Luo Ge
and Luo Ning.
I can't do anything wrong to them anymore.
Brother.
What else do you want to say?
Did you really not find Luo Ning's immortal energy?
No.
Luo Ning's death
was caused by our marriage.
I wronged her.
The Demon Palace is even more indebted to her.
And me.
It's my fault.
Even if I die hundreds or thousands of times,
it is still not enough.
You made such a huge mistake.
Luo Ge and the Immortal Palace should decide your fate.
I will continue to search for her immortal energy
at the Great Wilderness and the Demon Palace where she died.
If I can find it,
it'll be something to remember her by.
Take good care of him.
But don't untie
his chains.
Guard more carefully.
Check the boundary three times a day.
Yes.
Love
is the most consuming thing.
If you encounter it,
it'll be unknown whether it is a blessing or not.
If you encounter it, it'll be a blessing.
But what if the ending is unfortunate?
As long as it's my choice,
whether it is
good or bad,
I'll have no regrets.
Even if she knew the ending was like this,
Luo Ning still forgave Fu.
Just like ten thousand years ago,
Ze Shui fell in love with the Demon King.
I just want my brother to know
I must become the Demon Queen
and marry He Na.
I promise
I will be happy.
Brother.
Luo Ning.
Let him go.
Luo Ning! Luo Ning!
Luo Ning!
Maybe I was wrong from the beginning.
I shouldn't have stopped her from doing what she wanted.
I should've let her live the way she wanted.
I love it.
You're the best.
If I knew it sooner,
I wouldn't have asked her to copy any scriptures.
I would let her be free to see the outside world.
Maybe
this wouldn't have happened.
Luo Ning and Ze Shui
are both obsessed with love.
Maybe the men they love
are their inexorable doom.
They can't escape
or hide from them.
But there're no regrets
in love.
Yes.
Even if she met Fu,
even if she forgot everything,
in the end, there was only forgiveness and pardon left.
There was no resentment or regret.
But I still remember
I always
wanted to...
Luo Ning.
Break the curse for one person.
Is it
you?
Liu Shao.
During the time Luo Ning left,
I'm glad to have you by my side,
so I didn't fall into depravity.
So no matter what happens,
we should never let go
or give up.
Luo Ning.
What else do you need?
I'll find it for you.
I don't need anything.
I just
came back to see you.
Then,
I'm leaving.
You're leaving?
Where are you going?
To
a very cold and dark place.
But my brother is there.
I'm not afraid.
Take me with you.
I can't take you with me.
But
you can come to me.
Remember to come to me.
I'll take the perfume
with me.
That place
is really boring.
So,
you must come.
I'll wait for you.
Luo Ning.
Who took Luo Ning's things?
Could it really be Luo Ning?
No.
Luo Ning is dead.
And
I killed her myself.
That's right.
It was you
who killed Luo Ning.
Old man.
It's you.
You are the reason why I was in conflict with my brother.
You are the reason why I was in conflict with the Immortal Palace,
which led to Luo Ning's death.
Fu,
you're being unfair.
Did I ask you to steal the bride?
Did I ask you to give Luo Ning the Phoenix Tears?
Or did I ask you to set up traps
in the desert
and put your brother and your beloved
in danger?
It's me.
But don't be so sure.
You still have a chance.
Impossible.
Luo Ning is dead.
She won't show up again.
But her immortal energy
and the immortal energy of Ze Shui are one.
However,
the one under the Monument
hid it under the Four Seasons Monument.
What did you say?
The immortal energy is hidden under the Four Seasons Monument.
It's sealed with many boundaries.
Naturally, even Luo Ge couldn't find it.
If we break the Four Seasons Monument
and release him to ascend to an immortal.
By then, it won't be so difficult
for him to save Luo Ning
with his divine power.
Really?
Luo Ning could be saved?
First,
you need to help him ascend to an immortal.
I'm going to
a very cold and dark place.
The very cold and dark place
is under the Four Seasons Monument.
Could it be that
you don't want to save her?
Who are you?
That's right.
It's you.
I can help you save Luo Ning.
Do you want to save her?
Do you want freedom?
Do you want to revive Luo Ning?
Luo Ning.
As long as you listen to me
and obey me,
I will give you the power to overturn the three worlds.
Not only will I revive Luo Ning,
I will also revive
your children.
A servant
must act like a servant.
You must come to me.
I'll wait for you.
The immortal energy of Luo Ning is under the Four Seasons Monument.
If you break the Four Seasons Monument,
I'll help you revive her.
The younger generation of the clan has mostly migrated to the land.
With their cultivation
and the prestige you've built over the years,
it will not be difficult
to do something great.
It seems the Aquatic Demons...
No.
It's almost time for the Melody Race
to regain our prestige.
Your Majesty.
The situation of our clan is getting better.
Please take care of yourself.
In the battle in the Great Wilderness,
your organs were badly injured.
And you held on to exorcise the evil spirit for General Fu.
Thanks to the power of the water energy, you held on to now.
It's time to recuperate for some time.
I know.
This will have to wait after I take Fu to confess his crime at the Immortal Palace.
If I don't do these,
my heart will never be at ease.
Fu!
What's wrong, Fu?
What happened?
There is an evil spirit
combined with your spirit vein.
It can't be removed at all.
Because
I volunteered to let him control my spirit vein.
In exchange,
I can borrow some of his power of Supreme God.
What did you say?
But to deal with Luo Ge
and the entire Immortal Palace,
it's still a long way off.
Fu.
Do you know what you are doing?
I know exactly what I want.
What I want
is your power.
Have you forgotten why Luo Ning died?
I just can't forget how she died.
I must find her.
Fu.
Luo Ning is dead.
She can't come back to life.
She's not.
Don't keep making mistakes.
She's not dead.
As long as I get her immortal energy,
she can come back to life.
I dreamed of her yesterday.
She told me
she was trapped under the Four Seasons Monument.
It's dark and cold there.
She's waiting for me to pick her up.
So I must break the Four Seasons Monument.
I must save her.
Don't put the three worlds in danger
because of your personal interest.
Brother.
At this moment, I can't think that much anymore.
This time,
I just want to save Luo Ning.
Save Luo Ning
and our child.
In a few months,
a lovely child would have been born.
That's all I want.
You
love me so much.
I believe this time
you will help me too.
I need to borrow your water energy
to have enough power
to break the Four Seasons Monument.
Fu,
you will
regret it.
Brother,
you once conquered the entire demon world
in exchange for my freedom.
And now,
I want to use your water energy.
After I rescue Luo Ning,
you can do whatever you want.
You can even cut me into a thousand pieces.
Brother.
I'm sorry.
Fu.
I saw it clearly.
After observing the Seal of the Sun for so many times,
I finally see clearly.
I've grasped
the way to seal the sun.
But what happened back then
that made God of the Sun
so sad?
God of the Moonlight.
Luo Ge.
Liu Shao.
I've heard about
the thing Crown Wheel told you.
So,
the two Gods were really incompatible as fire and water.
Actually,
the Sun and the Moonlight loved each other deeply.
They are in charge of the sun and the moon.
They shouldn't have met.
But they fell in love at first sight
in the Yin-yang Cave.
But after they fell in love,
the sun eclipsed,
causing abnormal celestial phenomena.
The three worlds were in chaos.
For the sake of all beings,
they had to separate
and cultivate in seclusion separately.
Since they had separated at that time,
why
did all those things happen?
When the two gods were in seclusion,
the Demon King died for Immortal Ze Shui.
The immortal world had no master.
The demon world had no leader.
All kinds of obsession in the mortal world is growing.
It accumulated in the world,
became a powerful evil spirit
and harmed
the people,
causing chaos in the three worlds.
When the God of the sun heard about it,
she decided to fight the evil spirit to the death.
The God of the Moonlight couldn't bear to see the God of the Sun like this.
In order to save the God of the Sun,
he absorbed the evil spirit
and sealed it with his own body.
Sealed it with his own body?
Then why did the God of the Sun kill him?
Because the God of the Moonlight absorbed too much evil spirit.
In the end, he was controlled by it.
He's no longer the same as before.
For the three worlds,
the God of the Sun had to kill the one she love.
You are not him.
I am him.
If you don't believe me,
you can see yourself.
One had compassion for the world,
and the other brought disaster and turmoil to the three worlds.
You are no longer him.
The God of the Sun used the sword with all her might,
and the God of the Moonlight's heart was split in two.
The half tainted by the evil spirit
was suppressed under the Four Seasons Monument.
The remaining half
is...
I always worry that
the evil creature and I each have half a heart of the God of the Moonlight.
If one day,
I was controlled by the evil creature
like the God of the Moonlight.
You are different from him.
You are neither that evil creature
nor the God of the Moonlight,
but Luo Ge.
You won't be devoured by the evil spirit like him.
I'm afraid I can't protect the three worlds
or you.
If that day really comes,
then
I'll be the one to protect you.
If you were the God of the Sun,
what would you have done?
I think I would've made the same choice.
Although she broke her lover's heart,
she avoided her lover
being used by that evil creature.
This is the greatest respect
to a Supreme God.
My brother has relapsed,
so he couldn't attend to his duties.
So he ordered me to temporarily take the title of Demon King,
lead all demons
and bring glory to the demon world.
Everyone.
Are you okay with that?
The Demon King in White has relapsed.
May I know
how badly is the Demon King in White hurt that
he had to pass the throne
to his brother?
That's right.
We are of one mind.
It doesn't matter
who is the king.
How badly is my brother hurt?
It's not that serious.
He just needs to rest.
When he recovers,
I will return the title of Demon King to him immediately.
By then,
I will still be an official
and a younger brother.
And he'll still be the king
and an older brother.
But we...
we submitted to
the Demon King in White,
not you.
In that case,
let's present ourselves
before the Demon King in White
after he recovered.
Let's go.
Go.
How come Fu
has the power of His Majesty's water energy?
You don't think I'm qualified?
You think I'm not as powerful as my brother
and can't keep the demon world under control, right?
I dare not.
In terms of cultivation,
no one can compare with you.
You're better than...
the Demon King in White.
It's my fault.
Please spare my life.
It's too late
to beg for mercy now.
Who else still has a second opinion?
We are convinced.
Greetings, our King.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
We are convinced.
Greetings, our King.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
We are convinced.
Greetings, our King.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Everyone, lead your subordinates
to get ready
to do something great
with me.
By then,
whether it is the demon world,
the human world
or that immortal world high above,
they will all
submit to me.
We are willing to follow you
to revitalize the Demons.
to conquer the three worlds
and revitalize the Demons.
Conquer the three worlds!
Revitalize the Demons!
Fu,
I indulged you too much these years
and caused such a disaster.
This time,
you will pay the price.
What?
He Na gave the title of Demon King
to Fu?
That's right.
The news
has been spreading in the three worlds.
He Na loves his brother too much.
Even if he's injured,
he should think about it.
Fu
looks like someone who will stir up trouble.
Now he has the power,
who knows what he might do?
Are you going to scald me to death?
I'm sorry.
Blow it for me.
You're here.
You knew I was coming,
so you were waiting for me.
Yes.
The demon world suddenly changed hands.
I wonder what happened.
Of course you're worry about He Na.
Aren't you worried about him?
If it weren't for his brother,
Luo Ning wouldn't have died in the demon world.
I don't want to see him.
Even if you don't want to see him,
if anything happens to him,
will you really stand by?
He Na has no precaution against his brother.
He might be set up.
But Fu
would never kill his brother.
Luo Ge.
I want to go to the Demon Palace
to ensure the safety of He Na.
It may not be a bad idea.
You've improved a lot on your cultivation.
I don't think you're inferior to Fu.
After you infiltrate the Demon Palace,
remember to be careful.
You'll have no problem getting out safely.
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
Besides, I have the Moon Bell.
I'll let you know if there's anything wrong.
Bye.
Your Majesty!
Mr. Tai.
Has Fu taken over the title of Demon King?